9 lives just isn't enough...
10 Lives is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Christopher Jenkins.
A pampered cat takes for granted the lucky hand he has been dealt after he is
rescued and loved by Rose, a kind-hearted and passionate student.
When he loses his ninth life, fate steps in to set
him on a transformative journey.
Beckett (voice), played by Mo Gilligan.
Rose (voice), played by Simone Ashley.
Grace (voice), played by Sophie Okonedo.
Kirk / Cameron (voice), played by Zayn Malik.
Larry (voice), played by Dylan Llewellyn.
Happy (voice), played by Jeremy Swift.
10 Lives is a 2024 animated fantasy comedy film directed by Chris Jenkins
from a screenplay by Jenkins, Karen Wengrod and Ken Cinnamon.
It was co-produced by Canada, United Kingdom, France and United States.
The film features the voices of Mo Gilligan, Simone Ashley, Sophie Okonedo, Zayn
Malik, Dylan Llewellyn, Jeremy Swift, Tabitha Cross and Bill Nighy.
The film is about a pampered housecat Beckett (Gilligan) —  who totally takes for granted the lucky hand he has been dealt; loved and rescued
by Rose, a kind-hearted and passionate student focused on saving the world's bee population — during and after his ninth life.
10 Lives had its world premiere on January 20, 2024, at the
Sundance Film Festival, Park City, Utah.
In the United Kingdom, the film was labeled as a Sky Original, where it
became available to watch on Sky Cinema and NOW on April 5, 2024.
The film explores themes of cat, animals, talking animal.
The tone is lighthearted.